softbankrobotics.com 2017-08-26

# Privacy Policy | Pepper Developer Portal

Jump to navigation

## You are here

  1. Home ›
  2. Privacy Policy

Last Updated: November 29th, 2016

 **Privacy Policy**

SoftBank Robotics America, Inc. (" **SBRA** ") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all users (“ **Users** ”) of our websites, products and services (collectively, the " **Services** "). This privacy policy (“ **Policy** ”) is intended to provide you with information on how we collect, use, share and store the information that you provide to us when you access the Services so that you can make appropriate choices for sharing information with us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use the Services.

The Services may include links to websites of our promotional partners and third party payment processors or service providers, our affiliates or other entities that we own or control. This Policy does not apply to third-party websites and services and treatment of any Personal Information you provide to those is subject to the applicable third party’s individual privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these third-party websites and services or of any other sites that are linked to or from the Services.

When we process Personal Information in the United States, we follow United States data protection and privacy regulations, which may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If we are made aware that a consumer’s country of residence is outside of the United States, that consumer will be directed to the appropriate SoftBank Robotics company.

We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the Policy the date it was last revised. We encourage you to review this Policy from time to time to make sure that you understand how any Personal Information you provide will be used. Your continued use of the Services following the posting of changes to this Policy will mean you accept those changes.

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Policy, please send an e-mail to [**privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com**](mailto:privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com) or write to us at the address below:

SoftBank Robotics America, Inc. Attn: Privacy Rights Administrator c/o Legal Department  
150 California St, San Francisco, California 94111, USA

Please be assured that any Personal Information that you provide in communications to the above email and postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you request it.

The terms of this Policy are incorporated into our Terms of Use. All capitalized terms used in this Policy without a definition have the meaning defined in the Terms of Use. Please review our Terms of Use at: <https://developer.softbankrobotics.com/us-en/terms>

**1\. Personal Information Defined**

"Personal Information" means information that specifically identifies any User (including without limitation, name, date of birth, address, telephone/mobile number, e-mail address, public online identifiers, or payment/billing information), and any other information that is required by applicable law to be treated as Personal Information (“ **Personal** **Information** ”).

Personal Information does not include "aggregate” or “anonymized” information, which is data we collect about a User’s, or group or category of Users’, use of the Services and/or other sites or services (including without limitation, demographic or preference information) from which individual identities or other Personal Information has been removed. If SBRA combines this information with Personal Information, SBRA will treat this information as Personal Information pursuant to this Policy.

 **2\. Collection of Personal Information**

We may collect Personal Information about our Users in several ways when you visit or use the Services:

 **Active Collection:** We collect certain information from you when you provide it, such as if you:

  * Create a customer account;
  * Apply or register for a pre-order;
  * Subscribe to one of our newsletters or other promotional content;
  * Participate in our community forums or chat rooms
  * Shop at one of our online stores;
  * Receive customer or technical support;
  * Participate in contests, events, or promotions; and
  * Participate in polls, surveys, or questionnaires. 

Typically, the Personal Information we collect collect includes: name; email address; telephone number; shipping and billing address; date of birth, and payment information for those applying or registering for a pre-order or purchasing products through the Services. Additionally, we may also collect demographic information such as your age, gender, country and zip code of residence, other geo-locational information, and preferences. This demographic information may be associated with your Personal Information. If this demographic information is connected with Personal Information, we will treat the demographic information as Personal Information.

 **Passive Collection:** Furthermore, SBRA may collect information regarding your behavior to better adapt our products and Services to your interests and to provide a better quality of Services. SBRA may on its own, or with the help of third party analytics tools, collect information concerning your and other Users’ purchasing habits and use of our products and Services. The information collected may contain the following, without limitation: device unique identity, including mobile and robot, tablet unique identifier or other device identifiers and settings, internet provider, carrier, operating system, hardware information, localization information, date and time spent on the Services, metrics and statistics, feature usage, advertising conversion rates, purchase history and other similar information. Taken alone, this information may not be Personal Information; however, if SBRA combines any of this information with Personal Information, SBRA will treat this information as Personal Information pursuant to this Policy.

 **Cookies:** SBRA may use cookies on the Services. A "cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that websites often store on a User's computer. Cookies are typically used to quickly identify a User's computer and to "remember" things about the User's visit. SBRA may set cookies for your web browser as you visit our websites, use our Services or visit a website where SBRA provides ads, content or analytics. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer, although this may affect your ability to shop online or to access certain features of our Services. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. In addition to SBRA using cookies on Services and our network of websites, SBRA may allow certain partners to set and access their cookies on your computer. These companies’ use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the SBRA Policy. Please review them carefully. For more information about cookies, please see [**http://www.allaboutcookies.org**](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/#_blank). Please note, if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect certain features on the Services.

 **Third Parties:** We may obtain certain information about you from third parties, including Personal Information. Please note: SBRA is not responsible for the privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties.

 **3\. Use and Sharing of Personal Information**

We do not require that website visitors reveal any personally identifying information in order to gain general access to our Services. However, if you prefer not to, or if you are not allowed by law to, disclose Personal Information, you will not be able to register and/or enjoy certain features of our Services. We use Personal Information we collect through the Services for the purposes described in this Policy.

For example:

  * To provide the Services, products or information you request and to process and complete any transactions in connection therewith;
  * To communicate with you and respond to your emails, submissions, questions, inquiries, comments, requests, and complaints and to provide customer service. For instance, we may use your email address to send you service announcements that tell you about updates to our Terms of Use or this Policy, changing in pricing, changes to the Services or our online service or customer support policies. We may also use your mobile telephone number to send you via text message information or customer support you request.
  * To monitor and analyze the Services usage and trends and otherwise measure the effectiveness of the Services or request feedback from you about the Services;
  * To send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages, to detect and prevent fraud, and to otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Services;
  * To conduct surveys, contests and sweepstakes;
  * To operate the Services, including, without limitation, payment processing and products delivery ;
  * To personalize and improve the Services and Users' experiences, to increase the functionality and User friendliness of the Services, to deliver advertisements, newsletters, coupons, promotions, rewards, awards or other content, or features that match User profiles or interests on the Services, and to provide recommendations as to third-party advertisements, content or features that may be of interest to Users on the Services;
  * To provide you with news and information about our third party events, activities, offers, promotions, products, and services we think will be of interest to you;
  * For any other purpose as described in this Policy or for which we notified you the information will be collected, used and shared and received your consent.

 **Interest Based Advertising:** We may use third party ad serving technologies that collect information as a result of ad serving in the Services, and then temporarily display advertisements on the Services and third party sites. The information collected and used for interest-based advertising may contain the following, without limitation: age and gender, number views of an advertisement, device (including mobile and robot) unique identity or other device identifiers and settings, information about your use of the products and Services and other Internet sites (including third party web pages and mobile Internet sites) viewed by you (as well as date and time viewed), advertisement(s) served, the advertisement(s)’ in game location and length, and your response to the advertisement(s) (if any). The analytics tools and ad serving technologies may use server log files, web beacons, cookies (as further described below), tracking pixels and other technologies to collect said information, and may combine the information collected on other SBRA products and services with information collected from other third party sites and mobile products and services and with demographic, advertisement, market and other analytics surveys. Taken alone, this information may not be Personal Information; however, if we combine any of this information with Personal Information to serve you such interest-based advertising, we will provide you an opportunity to opt-out of such combination and treat this information as Personal Information pursuant to this Policy. You can opt out of some third-party technology’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [**aboutads.info**](http://www.aboutads.info/) **.**

 **4\. Sharing of Personal Information with Third Parties**

We will only share the Personal Information we collect from you through the Services with third parties as described in this Policy or otherwise as detailed at the time of collection. For example, we may share Personal Information as follows:

  * With affiliates of SBRA, including, but not limited to, SoftBank Robotics Group Corp, SoftBank Robotics Corp, SoftBank Robotics Europe SAS and SoftBank Robotics China Inc.;
  * With vendors, consultants, and/or other service providers (" **Service** **Providers** ") who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation and/or promotion of the Services and who need access to such information to carry out their work;
  * With other Users of the Services on our forums or chat rooms; and
  * With promotional partners to send you coupons, promotions, rewards, awards and advertisements that may be of interest to you.

To the extent that third parties have access to your Personal Information, whenever possible, we will request that they follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Policy;

We will also use and share information, including Personal Information, for the purposes specifically described below:

 **Custom Content** : We may share the Personal Information collected by us pursuant to this Policy with promotional partners to display customized content on our Services or third party sites that we think will be of interest to you.

 **Social Networks/Third-Party Accounts :** By accessing the Services through a social network or other third party platform or service, or by connecting to a third party account, network, platform or service via one of our products and/or Services, you are authorizing SBRA to (1) collect, store, and use, in accordance with this Policy, any and all information that you agreed that the social network or other third party service could provide to SBRA based on your settings on your relevant account, the third party social network or service and (2) share any and all of your Personal Information with the social network or other third party service, through the third party service’s Application Programming Interface (API). Your agreement to this takes place when you connect with the third party network, platform or service via our products and/or services, and/or when you connect with, "accept" or "allow" (or similar terms) one of our applications through the third party platform or service.

 **Online Events and Promotions:** Your participation in online events and promotions may be conditional upon SBRA’s collection, use, storage, transmission and public display of statistical data  generated through your participation. This statistical data may include your Personal Information.

 **Purchase or Sale of Businesses:** From time to time, we may purchase a business or sell or transfer one or more of our businesses and your Personal Information may be transferred as a part of the purchase or sale/transfer. If we purchase a business, the Personal Information received with that business would be treated in accordance with this Policy, if it is practicable and permissible to do so. If we sell a business, whenever possible, we will include provisions in the sale agreement requiring the purchaser to treat your Personal Information in the same manner as required by this Policy. The provisions of this paragraph will also apply if we are sold as part of bankruptcy proceedings.

 **Disclosures required by law and to protect the security and safety of Users:** We will disclose Personal Information when we believe in good faith that such disclosures (a) are required by law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena, (b) will help to: enforce this Policy or our Terms of Use; or enforce contest, sweepstakes, or promotions rules, (c) will protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or, protect the safety and security of SBRA, or any third parties. Unless required by law, SBRA will not be required to notify you of any such disclosure.

You understand that when you use the Services, any information you share with individuals through our forums or chat rooms or our other Services or through social network sites or other social feeds, will be available to other Users and in some cases may be publicly available. We recommend you be cautious about giving out Personal Information to others or sharing Personal Information in public or private online forums. Except to the extent required by applicable law, we are not responsible for the actions of third party service providers or other third parties, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to any third parties. Therefore, we encourage you to become familiar with their privacy practices before disclosing information directly to any such third parties.

 **5\. User Choices**

You have choices as to how we use the Personal Information you submit to us:

 **Promotional E-mails:** Once you register to our Services and/or purchase one of our products, SBRA may send you promotional communications about its Services that you may be interested in. If you do not wish to receive promotional e-mails from SBRA, please follow one of these two options: (a) when you receive a promotional e-mail from us, it will contain a link or other instruction that allows you to stop the delivery of similar messages from; us and/or (2) contact us at [**support@softbankrobotics.com**](mailto:support@softbankrobotics.com) or [**privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com**](mailto:privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com) with your request. If you decide to opt-out of receiving promotional e-mails, you will no longer receive special offers, valuable coupons, new product introductions or e-newsletters from SBRA. However, you will continue to receive non-promotional communications from us, such as order confirmations and/or important notifications about the Services and / or your account(s). Your opt-out request will be processed within thirty (30) days of the date of which we receive it.

 **Opt-Out of Custom Content:** We may work with trusted marketing partners to bring you more useful and interesting content on our Services and on third party sites and services. We may do this by sharing or matching the Personal Information you have provided on the Services with the information (which may include Personal Information) you have provided to third party marketing partners. If you do not want SBRA to match your Personal Information with trusted partners to tailor ads or other custom content for you on our Services and/or third party sites, you can contact [privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com](mailto:privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com). If you opt-out, SBRA will no longer share your Personal Information with partners to tailor ads or other custom content. Your opt-out request will be processed within thirty (30) days of the date of which we receive it.

Opting-out from the Custom Content will not change the behavior of third parties collecting information on the Services. For more information as to how to opt-out of third party collection please contact [privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com](mailto:privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com)

 **Do not Track:** SBRA does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) settings in your browser.

 **Your California Privacy Rights** : The following applies solely to California residents who have an established business relationship with SBRA. If we collect Personal Information from you, we may make that Personal Information available to third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. If you decide that you do not want us to share your Personal Information with these companies for their marketing and promotional purposes, please send an e-mail to [**privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com**](mailto:privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com). In this email, state that you would like SBRA to not share your Personal Information with third parties for their marketing purposes. Your opt-out request will be processed within thirty (30) days of the date of which we receive it.

 **6\. Policy for Children**

SBRA does not knowingly collect personally identifying information from children under 13 years of age via our Services.

 **7\. Safeguard of Personal Information**

The security and confidentiality of your Personal Information is extremely important to us. We use robust security measures to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse and alteration. We use industry-standard practices such as encrypted communications, physically secured rooms, firewalls and password protection systems to safeguard the confidentiality of your Personal Information. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. However, please understand that, despite our best efforts, no security measure is perfect or impenetrable. We will notify Users of a data breach as required by applicable law **.**

To protect the confidentiality of Personal Information maintained in your account, you must keep your log-in information and password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Services by any person using your log-in information and/or password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your log-in and/or password has been misused.

DESPITE OUR EFFORTS TO KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE, NO COMPANY CAN GUARANTY THE SECURITY AND PRIVACY OF ITS SERVICES, INFORMATION AND OTHER DATA. ACCORDINGLY, SBRA DISCLAIMS AND DOES NOT REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT IT WILL BE ABLE TO MAINTAIN YOUR PRIVACY OR THE SECURITY OF ITS DATA IN REGARD TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. OUR PRIVACY POLICIES AND PROCEDURES ARE "AS IS" AND SBRA MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS AS TO THE FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR MERCHANTABILITY OF ITS SERVICES.

 **8\. Storage and Use Period**

Unless a different storage or use period is required by applicable laws and regulations, SBRA will use and store your Personal Information for the length of time we think is necessary for the uses outlined in this Policy.

 **9\. Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information**

You can access and update the contact information you gave us during registration (that is, your e-mail address or any other information that would directly enable us to contact you), by logging in and clicking the Edit Profile section, or contacting us at [**privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com**](mailto:privacy_us@softbankrobotics.com). You may be required to provide additional information in order for us to verify your request. Your request will be processed within thirty (30) days of the date of which we receive it.

## Pepper Developer Newsletter

Exit

Exit

## プロジェクトの送信

Imagine your project featured in our Pepper Showcase. Give us your details, a brief description of your project and any links to images or videos. If we like the sound of it, your work could be featured on this site.
